(Lucy:)Why were you acting so strange tonight?
You called me "feminine."
(Raj:)I wanted you to think I was more manly.
(Lucy:)Raj, I didn't say feminine was a bad thing.
I meant you're sweet and thoughtful
and your skin looks so much like caramel...
(Lucy:)...I just want to dip an apple in your face.
(Raj:)I do have a pretty balls-to-the-wall
moisturizing regimen.
(Lucy:)So are you okay?
(Sheldon(on phone):)- Yeah.
- Good.
(Lucy:)- Do you even like hockey?
- Heh. No.
I bought this at the Staples Center
when I went to see Taylor Swift.
(Penny:)So I was thinking how excited you get
about stuff like Buffy or science...
(Penny:)...or which TV remote
you and Sheldon should buy...
(Leonard:)The Harmony One was fine.
We didn't need the 1100...
(Leonard:)...which he knows is too big for my hand.
(Penny:)See, that's the kind of passion
I didn't think I had.
(Penny:)But then I realized
I'm passionate about you.